<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Logdog</string>
    <string name="long_text">零零零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零零九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零一九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零二九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零三九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零四九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五零赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五一赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五二赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五三赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五四赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五五赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五六赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五七赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五八赤橙黄绿青蓝紫零五九赤橙黄绿青蓝紫</string>
</resources>
